{
    "id": "512766030efc479c85186c5e94a2807a",
    "title": "Rewrite as directed | grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "5731ac1510754f02b286ee711c0e45c5",
            "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "English ................................ all over the world.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "speaks",
                        "is spoken"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The thief .................................. by the police.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has arrested",
                        "has been arrested"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The show ....................................... by both men and women.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is watching",
                        "is being watched"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Football .................................... all over the world.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is playing",
                        "is played"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The national anthem .................................... by the boys.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was singing",
                        "was being sung"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The match will certainly ....................................... by our team.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "won",
                        "be won"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The news ............................................... yet.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hasn't announced",
                        "hasn't been announced"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The answers are to ..................................... on both sides of the paper.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "write",
                        "be written",
                        "be writing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has always ..................................... by his supporters.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "admired",
                        "been admired",
                        "been admiring"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The roof is ....................................... by the contractor.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "fixing",
                        "being fixing",
                        "being fixed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}